Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory02 Mss.B.B61.inventory02
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents B
  - Bernays, Edward L. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 30; 1p
  - Berne, Lewis A. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1940 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 22; 1p
  - Bernheim, Felix (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 18; 1p
  - Bernstein, David (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 July 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 18; 1p
  - Bernstein, Felix (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 22; 2p
    - F. Bernstein -- from F&D Fackenthal, 1936 June 17
  - Bernstein, J.L. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Bernstein, Ludwig B. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 July 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 July 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 8; 4p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 8; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 8; 1p
  - Bernstein, Victor H. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1935 July 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov.?; 1p
  - Bernstorff, Count J. H. von (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 May 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 28
  - Berntz, Jos. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 6; 1p
  - Bernus,? von (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 25; 1p
  - Berrien, Wm. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 3; 1p
  - Berscheim, G. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 24; 1p
  - Bersling, K.O. (Box 7)
    see Bertling, K.O.
  - Bertha (Box 7)
    See Edel, Bertha C.
  - Bertheau, R.C. (Box 7)
    - From Tinney, M.C., enc. with Osborn, F., 1938 Feb. 18
    - From Tinney, M.C., enc. with Osborn, F., 1938 Mar. 11
  - Berthelson, Mrs. E.M. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 26; 1p
  - Bertholet (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 30; 2p
  - Bertling, K.O. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept 19; 1p
  - Bertram, J. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1911 June 23
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 3
    - JB -- to McAneny, G., 1918 Apr. 16
  - Berwanger, A.B. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1928 July 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 31; 1p
  - Besdine, Lillian (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 3; 1p
  - Bessels, C. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1885 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1885 July 20
    - To Boas, 1885 July 27
  - Bessels, Emil (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 2p
    - To Boas, 1884 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1884 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1884 Nov. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1884 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1884 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1885 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1886??
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1886 June 4
    - To Boas, 1886 June 5
    - To Boas, 1886 July 2
  - Bessemans, A. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Betti, A. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1918 Sept. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 15; 4p
  - Bettinger, Albert (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 13; 1p
  - Bettings, B. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 8; 1p
  - Bettle, G.G. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 193 Sept. 13; 1p
  - Betz (Box 7)
    - From Heuser, F.W.J., 1922 Dec. 6; 2p
  - Betz, W. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 3p
  - Beukes, W.T.H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 5
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug.; 2p
    - WTHB -- to Fackenthal, F.D., 1932 Nov. 12; 2p
    - WTHB -- from Fackenthal, F.D., 1932 Dec. 15
  - Beveridge, W. (Box 7)
    - From Szilard, enc. with Liebowitz, B. to Boas E.P., 1933 May 4
  - Bewer, Julius A. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 20; 2p
      - see Speyer, J., 1920 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 27; 1p
  - Beyer, H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 10; 2p
  - Beyer, Henry G. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 29
  - Beyer, H.O. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1917 July 25
  - Beyer, Hermann (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 6; 2p
  - Beyer, Silva S. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 20; 1p
    - SSB -- from Gordon, P.W., 1933 June 23; 1p
  - Beynon, William (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sept. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec.?; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 July 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 July 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Jan. 5
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 Jan.?
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Feb. 7
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Mar. 11
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 Mar.?
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Apr. 6
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 May 12
    - To Boas bill, 1938 May?
    - To Boas bill, 1938 June 17
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 June?
    - To Boas bill, 1938 July 22
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 July?
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 Aug.?
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Sept. 6
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Oct. 3
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Oct. 28
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 Oct.?
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas receipt, 1938 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas bill, 1938 Nov. 30
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Jan. 27
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Feb. 12
    - To Boas bill, 1939 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Aug. 4; 3p
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Oct. 9
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Oct. 27; 2p
    - To Boas receipt, 1939 Oct.?
    - To Boas receipt, 1939 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Nov. 1
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas bill, 1939 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas receipt, 1939 Dec.?
    - To Boas receipt, 1940 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas receipt, 1940 June 10; 1p
    - To Boas bill, 1940 July 29
    - To Boas bill, 1940 Aug. 3; 3p
    - WB -- to Susman, A., 1940 July 1; 1p
    - see Susman, A., 1940 Aug. 10
  - Bezold, C. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 July 6; 2p
    - Bezold -- to Kirchhoff, 1886 Feb. 20
  - Bickel, B. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 21; 4p
  - Bickmore, Albert Smith (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1887 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 12
    - ASB -- to Abraham Jacobi, 1889 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1888 May 26
  - Biddle, Francis (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 12; 1p
      (enc. F. Boas to Roosevelt, F.D.)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Bieber, Margarete (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec.?; 1p
  - Bielaski, A.B. (Box 7)
    - ABB -- to Chamberlain, G.E., 1918 Jan. 4; 1p
    - ABB -- to Hervey, W.A., 1917 Nov. 3
    - ABB -- to Young, A.A., 1917 Dec. 4
  - Biermann, F.H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Biermont, P. de (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1914 July 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 15; 2p
  - Bigelow, A.J. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 21; 1p
  - Bigelow, G.E. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 12; 2p
  - Bigingian (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 11
  - Bigley, K. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 25; 2p
  - Bijur, Harry (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 29; 1p
  - Bilby, J.W. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 11; 6p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr.; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 1; 2p
  - Bilden, Rüdiger (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sept. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 26; 1p
    - See enc. FB to Kapper, P., 1933 Apr. 18
    - See enc. FB to Moe, H.A., 1936 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 15; 1p
    - RB -- from Dannemann, E., 1933 Nov. 18
  - Bilhuber, E. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20; 1p
  - Bill, C.P. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p
  - Billikopf, J. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1938 May 12; 1p
      - enc. JB to Golomshtok, E.A. June 7, 1941 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p
      - enc. JB to Rosenwald, L.J., 1934 Feb. 13; 1p
  - Billinger, G. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1905 May 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 26
  - Billings, Johns S. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 21; 5p
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 28
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1887 May 14
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1910 May 31
  - Billingsley, Mr. and Mrs. (Box 7)
    - 1928 Dec. 17
  - Binder, Rudolph M. (Box 7)
    - see FB open letter RE Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Bing, Gertrud (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 15; 1p
  - Bingham (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 2
  - Bingham, Alfred M. (Box 7)
    - from Sargent, Porter, 1941 June 27
    - enc. Sargent, Porter, 1941 July 8
  - Bingham, H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 24
    - HB -- to Angell, J.R., 1925 Feb. 18
  - Bingham, T.A. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1909 May 12
  - Bingham, W.V. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept 13; 1p
    - WVB -- to Nat'l Research Coun., Div. Anthrop. & Psychol., 1919 Nov. 28; 1p
    - WVB -- to Nat'l Research Coun., Div. Anthrop. & Psychol., 1919 Dec. 28; 1p
  - Biologische Versuchsanstalt Vienna, Austria (Box 7)
    See Przibram, Hans
  - Bird, Henry (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1942 May 4; 1p
  - Birket-Smith, Kaj (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 June 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sept. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 June 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 26; 2p
      enc. KB-S to Commit.
      - Intern'l Res. in Arctic ethn., 1936 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 11; 1p
    - KB-S -- to Rocier, C. de la, 1933 Feb. 24; 4p
  - Birkhoff, George D. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Birnbaum (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 31; 1p
    - enc. with Kallmann, Franz, 1936 Oct. 26
  - Birnham, B.J. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Biro, J. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 12
  - Biro-Bidjan, People's delegation to (Box 7)
    - Add. list of endorsements, 1936 Dec.
  - Bishop, Carl W. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 July 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 15
  - Bishop, H.R. (Box 7)
    - To A.S. Bickmore, 1887 Feb. 23
  - Bishop, W.W. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Bishop of Vancouver Isle (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 27
  - Bissell, Frank (Box 7)
    - To E.P. Boas, 1942 Dec. 23; 1p
  - Bixby, W.K. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 14; 3p
  - Black, A.D. (Box 7)
    - To E.P. Boas, 1942 Dec. 28; 1p
  - Black, John C. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 4
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 May 1
  - Black, W.H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 21; 1p
      - enc. FB to Thompson, D., 1939 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 4; 1p
  - Blackfan, Kenneth D. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 21; 1p
    - KDB -- to Franzen, Dr. Raymond, 1930 Mar. 28; 2p
  - Blackmar, Frank W. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 25
  - Blair, Clyde M. (Box 7)
    - From Meritt, E.B., 1927 June 2
  - Blair, K. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1924 May 9; 1p
  - Blaisdell, James A. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 8; 1p
  - Blake, H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 25; 1p
  - Blake, Robert P. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 22; 2p
  - Blakely, Clarence L. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 13; 1p
  - Blakeslee, A.F. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas with enc., 1941 Oct. 21; 1p
  - Blakeslee, George H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1919 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 July 11
  - Blanchard, Paul (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 11; 1p
      - open letter, Labor Party, 1940 Feb.
  - Blanchard, W. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 14
  - Blancquaert, E. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 3; 1p
  - blank (Box 7)
    - petition urging war, 1941 Oct. 1; 1p
  - Blankenhorn, M. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 29; 4p
  - Blanton, R. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 14; 1p
  - Blau, Arthur (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 4; 2p
    - rough draft, 1937 Feb. 4; 2p
  - Bleecker, E. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 12; 1p
  - Bleeker, Sonia E. (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1938 May 10; 1p
  - Blegen, T.C. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 9; 1p
  - Blish, Helen H. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Bliss, Cornelius N. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 25; 1p
  - Bliss, R.W. (Box 7)
    - To Boas
      (honorary membership diploma, Hamburg Geographical Soc.)
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 17; 1p
  - Bliven, B., Jr. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 4; 1p
    - BB -- from Viereck, G.S., 1935 Oct. 1
      - enc. with Viereck, G.S., 1935 Oct. 21
  - Bloch, Bernard (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Bloch, Emanuel (Box 7)
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 21; 1p
  - Block, H.W. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 15; 1p
  - Blom, F. (Box 7)
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 29; 1p
    - Blom -- from Danforth, C.H., 1931 June 29
  - Blondel, Charles (Box 7)
    - See Bouglé, C., 1931 Mar. 15
      - co-signers: Fauconnet
      - Gilson, Rivet
      - Rivaud, Mauss
  - Bloomfield, Leonard (Box 7)
    - 1924 Jan. 26, 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 26 & Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 9; 2p
    - From Boas not in file, 1927 Apr. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 9; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir) not in file, 1927 May 10; 4p
    - From Boas not in file, 1927 May 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 July 20; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1927 Sept 28; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1927 Oct. 4; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1927 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 28; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1927 Nov. 7; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1927 Nov. 14; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1927 Dec. 1; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1927 Dec. 31; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1928 Jan. 7; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1928 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 5; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1928 Apr. 12; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1928 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Jan. 14; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Jan. 29; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Feb. 14; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Mar. 6; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Mar. 13; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Mar. 25; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Apr. 1; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Apr. 1; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Apr. 11; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Apr. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 6; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 May 7; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 10; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 July 24; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Oct. 2; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Oct. 2; 2p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Oct. 4; 2p
    - From Boas
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Oct. 21; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Nov. 11; 1p
      - (& to E. Sapir), 1929 Dec. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 2; 1p
      - (& to Kroeber, A.L.), 1939 May 5; 1p
      - (& to Swadesh, M.), 1939 June 22
    - From Boas not in file, 1939 July 13; 1p
      - (& to Kroeber, Sapir, & Swadesh), 1939 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 29; 2p
      - (& to Kroeber, Hoijer & Swadesh), 1940 May 31; 1p
      - (& to Kroeber, Hoijer & Swadesh), 1940 July 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 4; 1p
      - see FB to Swadesh, 1941 Feb. 6
      - see FB to Hoijer, H., 1941 July 31
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Sept 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Sept 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 12; 1p
      - see FB to Kroeber, A., 1942 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 13; 1p
      - (& from Bolling, G. & Sturtevant, E.), 1924 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas not in file, 1924 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 17; 1p
      - (enc. Oldfather, W.A. to LB), 1926 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 19 & Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 23; 1p
    - To Boas not in file, 1933 July 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 4; 1p